vocabulary.co.il 2019-05-21

# Privacy Policy | Legal

Privacy Policy Updated: June 2013

At Vocabulary.co.il, we consider children’s safety–which is related to privacy–to be all-important.

Our site complies with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act “COPPA”, which you may read about [here](http://www.coppa.org/comply.htm).

Our site complies with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act “COPPA”, which you may read about here.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully because it describes our privacy practices and helps distinguish our service from others which have different policies. If you have questions or comments on our policy, we would very much like to hear from you using the contact us function on the website.

Vocabulary.co.il service – provides a variety of online vocabulary games and resources. Registration is not required and we never store any game data. The only contact information that is collected is from parents interested in receiving our newsletter. www.vocabulary.co.il will never seek to directly contact children under 14 years of age.

## Supervision

Children on the internet should be closely supervised and instructed about security, and this is the parent’s responsibility. We recommend that parents provide the following information to all children: [Kids’ Rules for Online Safety](http://www.safekids.com/kids-rules-for-online-safety/).

## What about the collection of information by third parties?

Our web site contains links to web sites not maintained by Vocabulary.co.il. The privacy and data collection practices on any linked web sites are entirely separate from those of Vocabulary.co.il and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. We cannot guarantee that student users will not go to another site where personal information from them is solicited. Vocabulary.co.il does have limited advertising on the site and takes measures to maintain the appropriateness of the advertising material to the educational mission of Vocabulary.co.il. Google’s Adsense service is our primary supplier of advertising; Google’s activities include placing “cookies” on user computers in order to track user movement through various websites on the internet.

### *What is a cookie?

A cookie is information a web site puts on your computer’s hard drive so that the site can remember your preferences or which pages you visited on that site.

## Children’s Privacy Guidelines

Vocabulary.co.il exists to serve educators, parents and students and strives to provide a safe, positive experience for children. To ensure this, we adhere to the following policies:

  1. We do not collect online contact information directly from children ages 13 and younger.
  2. We do not distribute any personally identifiable information about children to third parties.
  3. We do not allow students to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent.
  4. We try to avoid providing access to any web sites that request personal information, such as user email or physical addresses.
  5. We do not use the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to entice children to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.

Your family’s use of this site is conditioned on and deemed to constitute your acceptance of these terms. You should return to and review this policy frequently, since it is subject to modification from time to time without notice, and your continued use of the site is conditioned upon and deemed to constitute your acceptance of any such modifications.

Vocabulary.co.il is supported in part by Time4Learning.com and Time4Writing.com. Time4Learning.com is an online learning service popular as a [homeschool curriculum](https://www.time4learning.com/homeschool-curriculum.htm), for [afterschool supplementary education](https://www.time4learning.com/learning-enrichment.shtml), and for [summer skills sharpening](https://www.time4learning.com/summer-school.shtml). Time4Writing.com provides unique online services that help [students learning to write](https://www.time4writing.com/).

### Notice to California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights

Effective January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Secton 1798.83 permist our customers who are California residents to request cerain information regarding our dislcosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at:

Vocabulary.co.il  
Attention: California Privacy Rights Request  
6300 NE 1st Ave, Ste 203  
Ft. Lauderdale, FL 33334
